http://www.famousplayers.com/Global/PrivacyPolicy?cmpid=FooterEN_privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Cineplex Entertainment LP: Guest Privacy Policy (the "Privacy Policy")
Effective Date: October 24, 2019
At Cineplex Entertainment LP, we share your concerns about the privacy and protection of your personal information. This Privacy Policy describes the steps we have taken and our practices regarding the protection of your Personal Information (as defined below).
This Privacy Policy applies to Cineplex Entertainment LP and its wholly owned subsidiaries, affiliates, and related entities (collectively, “Cineplex” or “our”, “we”, or “us”). The contents of this Privacy Policy are intended to be read and understood in accordance and compliance with all applicable privacy laws, statutes, and regulations in the jurisdictions where Cineplex operates. Please note the following entities and websites are not governed by this Privacy Policy: SCENE GP, SCENE.ca, WorldGaming Network LP, WorldGaming.com, Player One Amusement Group Inc. and WinWithP1AG.com
If you have not already done so, we encourage you to familiarize yourself with this Privacy Policy before using any Cineplex website, automated kiosk, or application (collectively the "Applications” and/or “Websites"), purchasing Cineplex products or services, applying for an employment opportunity with Cineplex, or visiting our physical locations. The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to inform our visitors, guests, job applicants, customers and other individuals with whom we deal ("you" and "your") about how we collect, use, share and protect Personal Information. This Privacy Policy applies to the collection, use, sharing and protection of your Personal Information by Cineplex. Your dealings with Cineplex and all of its associated brands (Cineplex Cinemas, Cineplex Odeon, Cineplex Digital Media, Famous Players, Galaxy, SilverCity, StarCité, Colossus, Coliseum, Colisée, Scotiabank Theatre, Cinema City, Playdium, TopGolf Canada, and The Rec Room) are also governed by this Privacy Policy.
Your use of our Applications and Websites is further governed under the applicable Terms of Use as indicated on such Applications and Websites.
Definition of Personal Information
Personal Information is information about an identifiable individual including, without limitation, information such as your name, address, birth date, and personal contact information and other information as described below. It may also include other types of more technical information such as IP addresses, geolocation, device ID, or browsing history in connection with our Applications or Websites, but only when this information can identify you as an individual. Information that is aggregated and cannot be associated with an identifiable individual is not considered to be Personal Information.
Personal Information We Collect Directly from You
Cineplex and its employees, agents, contractors, service providers, partners and representatives may collect the following Personal Information that you provide to us directly:
Contact Information (e.g. name, home address, home or mobile telephone number or e-mail address) that you may provide to us, for instance, when you create a Cineplex Account, make an inquiry or contact us in person or through our Applications or Websites, by telephone, email, SMS, social media, or any other means of electronic communication;
Credit or Debit Card Information, including card number, expiry date and CVS/CVV code that you may provide to us, for instance, when purchasing theatre tickets or other products or services;
Information relevant to a particular service you request (e.g. the age and gender of a child or other person where you request our birthday party services);
Survey Responses (e.g. when you provide your name or other contact information in order to take part in a survey);
Preferences and other Personal Information provided by you through our Applications or Website (e.g. including but not limited to local theatre preferences, favourite movie genres, movie reviews, and comments);
Job Applications (e.g. information you provide to us when applying for an employment opportunity by sending us a resume or by submitting a job application). All Personal Information and Applicant Information provided by you and during the application process must be true, complete and correct to the best of your knowledge. Any misrepresentation or omission of facts may result in refusal to hire or, if hired, may result in your dismissal at any time regardless of when the false answer or omissions are discovered. Please do not include any sensitive information in your application, such as unique identifiers (such as social insurance numbers) or financial information.
Personal Information We Collect Automatically
In some cases, we may collect information automatically which may not necessarily identify you as an individual. For instance, we may collect the following type of information:
Video Surveillance. As a security measure and in order to ensure the safety of our properties, we use video surveillance technology at our physical locations. This collection is subject to applicable privacy laws and may be shared only in limited circumstances, as detailed in the Sharing of Personal Information section of this Privacy Policy.
Traffic and Device Count. We may use cameras and other technologies (ex. anonymous video analytics and anonymous traffic analysis) at our physical locations or advertising installations to better understand traffic patterns and aggregate demographics about guests at our physical locations or about those who interact with our advertising installations. These practices allow us to track the number of individuals at a specific location and to understand some basic demographic information, such as gender and age, but these technologies do not personally identify or store photos or videos of individuals. We may also track devices which have communicated with our Wi-Fi systems, but such tracking is conducted without the storage of information that is personally identifying or specific to your mobile device (ex. MAC addresses). This information is collected for the purpose of improving our staffing and services. In some circumstances, we may share the aggregated statistical information compiled through the use of these technologies with our business partners, including advertisers.
Technical Information. The nature of internet browsing is such that this activity passively and automatically collects and discloses certain information about each individual’s use of the internet. This information may be associated with an individual’s Internet Protocol ("IP") address. This is a unique internet "address" which is assigned to all internet users by their Internet Service Provider ("ISP"). Our server logs record statistical information, such as visitors' IP addresses, type of operating systems, time and duration of visit, webpages requested, as well as identifying categories of visitors by items such as domains and browser types.
Cookies. Our Applications and Websites make use of both "sessional" and "persistent" cookies or similar technologies. Cookies are small text files offered to your computer by Web servers in order to keep track of your browser settings as you navigate the site. Persistent cookies are stored on your hard drive. Sessional cookies are stored in temporary (cache) memory and are deleted when you shut down your browser or turn off your computer. We use these cookies or similar technologies to store your preferences, record session information such as language preferences, record user-specific information on what pages you access or visit, develop information about your preferences and interests, alert you to areas that we think might be of interest to you when you return to our site, record past activity in order to provide better service when you return to our site, help rotate banner advertising so as to ensure that visitors are not repeatedly sent the same banner ads, and customize Websites content based on your browser type or other information you provide. For each visit to our Websites, cookies or similar technologies may be used by our server to recognize you where you have indicated your preference to be automatically logged in. You may disable cookies using your browser's settings. Please consult your browser's help function for information on how to disable cookies. Note that if you disable cookies, certain features of our Websites will not function to their fullest potential.
Behavioural Advertising. To try and bring you offers that are of interest to you, Cineplex or its service providers place ads on our webpages. As a result of your visit to our Websites, or by clicking on these ads, we may collect passive information such as your domain type, your IP address and clickstream information. Some of the ads on our Websites are served through one or more reputable ad-serving companies, including but not limited to Google. These third parties may use information such as webpages you visit and cookies, to provide ads that may be of interest to you. In addition, we may use IP addresses to allow our third party advertising partners to display more targeted ads and content. Cineplex respects your right to control your advertising preferences. We are a member of the Interactive Advertising Bureau of Canada (IAB Canada), and we follow industry standards for online behavioural advertising, including standards set by the Digital Advertising Alliance Canada (DAAC). DAAC’s Ad Choices initiative allows you to opt-out from the use of your online activities for the purpose of serving ads based on your internet browsing history. Clicking on the Ad Choices logo on any ad will allow you to opt-out of online behavioural advertising from that advertiser. However, please note, Ad Choices uses cookies to work and it is specific to the browser you are using at the time. The services and tools provided by Ad Choices and the DAAC are provided by third parties and not Cineplex. We do not control or operate these services or tools. For more information about how you can manage your ad preference and control cookies please visit http://youradchoices.ca.
Social Media. If you sign into our Applications or Websites using a social media account such as Facebook or Twitter (“Social Media Platforms”), we will collect information that you have added in your registration profile from those accounts and which is made available to us by default by the relevant Social Media Platform. We may also collect Personal Information about you from your use of Social Media Platforms, through which you may allow us to collect (or the third party to share) Personal Information about you, such as details of your friends/connections, “likes”, comments you have shared, groups and location. In addition, we may receive Personal Information about you if other users of a third party website give us access to their profiles and you are one of their friends/connections or information about you is otherwise accessible through your friends’/connections’ web page, profile page, or similar page on a Social Media Platform or other third party website or interactive service. We may supplement the information we collect about you directly with the information we receive from third parties in order to enhance our ability to serve you, to tailor our content to you and send you details of promotions and/or offers which we believe may be of interest to you, although at all times, in compliance with applicable privacy laws.
Use of Your Personal Information
We collect and use Personal Information as permitted or required by law, with your consent or for the following purposes:
To process your purchases and reservations: We may use your Personal Information to process your purchases and reservations. For instance, personal contact and credit/debit card information will be used by Cineplex to process your purchases and reservations (this includes purchases made through our Applications or Websites or at one of our physical locations or through special event bookings, or the purchase or rental of movies through the Cineplex Store). For event bookings, such as birthday parties, the child's name, age and gender will be used to organize the event. In these cases, credit/debit card information is only used for the purposes required to process and complete the transaction and/or service requested by you, and is only retained in transaction records required for internal management and auditing purposes or as otherwise required by law, unless you are informed otherwise or you provide your consent.
For Theatre and The Rec Room Administration: Your name, address and telephone number may be stored by us should you provide such information, for instance when you use our lost-and-found or coat check services. Also, your name, address and telephone number may be collected and used by Cineplex for audit and refund verification purposes when you request a ticket refund. We may require identification to be provided to establish a person’s age for age-restricted movies, events or activities (such as virtual reality games), age restricted ticket purchases, access to our VIP cinemas, or the purchase of alcohol at any of our physical locations.
To Ensure the Security of our Properties: Cineplex uses video surveillance to monitor its physical locations for crime deterrence and detection purposes. In the event of accident or theft, Cineplex may collect, use and share information related to the incident or theft as required for operational, insurance, legal or other necessary purposes.
To Administer Contests: From time to time, Cineplex will administer contests at our physical locations, online, which may include partnerships with third-party business partners and third-party advertising clients through our Applications or Websites. We may request your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address and we may also require proof of age for the purposes of determining contest eligibility. Unless otherwise stated in the applicable contest rules, your Personal Information will only be used for prize notification and fulfilment and related purposes in connection with the contest, and only as authorized by law or in accordance with this Privacy Policy.
To Communicate with You: Subject to your right to withdraw consent and unsubscribe, we may use your Personal Information to communicate with you for the purposes of providing you with our newsletters, advertising and marketing messages pertaining to additional products or services that may be of interest to you on the quality of our products, services or customer service. Individuals who provide us with their telephone numbers will only receive communications from us with respect to orders, contests or other products or services that they have requested, unless they provide express consent to receive commercial telephone calls or SMS messages from us.
Surveys: Cineplex will occasionally conduct surveys and market research, at our physical locations, by telephone, in person, or on our Applications or Websites. These surveys and market research may ask you about your preferences in relation to our services, your age, gender, approximate location, or other information that may assist Cineplex in understanding the preferences of its visitors and guests. Your participation in such surveys or market research is entirely voluntary and, in some cases, you may be able to participate anonymously. Your contact information, including your name, address, telephone number and/or other Personal Information may be required: (1) to permit you to enjoy bonuses or benefits which may be available to survey or market research participants (in which case your contact information will only be used for notification or fulfillment purposes); or (2) where you have provided your express consent to us contacting you to discuss comments that you made during our surveys and/or market research. Except as described in this Privacy Policy, survey and/or research responses are only used by Cineplex on an aggregate basis.
To Improve and Customize our Applications or Websites: We use information which you provide to us on the Websites to facilitate your registration, to understand the identity of our guests and the nature of their preferences, to improve the content of the Applications or Websites, to customize the content and/or layout of our webpages for each visitor based on the information provided to us, to send you periodic newsletters and mailings that you request, to process your purchases and to conduct surveys, polls and contests.
To Create a Cineplex Account: When you register for an account on our Applications or Websites, make purchases, enter contests, respond to surveys, or otherwise participate in our online community, our servers may store your Personal Information, contact details or other information in order to facilitate login, the automatic completion of forms and other preferences for your convenience. If you prefer that we not store such information on our servers, you may select the appropriate option on the Applications or Websites (if that option is available) or you may contact us as indicated in the How to Contact Us section of this Privacy Policy.
Job Applicants: Your Personal Information and Applicant Information may be used to make hiring decisions, and to comply with applicable laws. Should you be hired, relevant portions of your Personal Information will be used to create and maintain your employment records. By providing Applicant Information, you agree that we may contact the employers, organizations, schools, professional associations provided by you, to verify the accuracy of such information.
Other Uses: We may also use Personal Information, where necessary, for:
establishing, maintaining and/or fulfilling relationships with our business partners, third-party vendors of products and/or services, as well as our corporate and business customers;
understanding and assessing the interests, wants and changing needs of customers with a view to improving our products and services and developing new ones (for instance, we may assess the types of movies our customers prefer to determine which types of movies to offer in the future);
evaluating job applications or resumes which are sent to us, as further described in the Job Application section below;
conducting operating, administering and otherwise managing our business, to satisfy legal, regulatory, security, audit, financial and processing requirements, or as otherwise permitted or required by law.
Sharing of Personal Information
Personal Information collected by Cineplex is not shared to other parties, except as permitted or required by law, with your express consent, or as follows:
We may share your Personal Information with outside parties who sponsor or otherwise participate in sweepstakes or other promotions, whether on our Applications or Websites or otherwise. We will inform you of the identity of these third parties at the time we collect your Personal Information.
Your Personal Information may be shared with our parent, subsidiary, affiliated and/or related corporations or entities, or to their employees, agents, contractors, representatives, servants, legal counsel and/or accountants without limitation, for operational, management and administrative purposes, as well as internal audit, legal, regulatory, security, insurance, financial, processing and other similar purposes, or as otherwise permitted or required by law.
Your Personal Information may be transferred to service providers, who may be affiliates of Cineplex, where such entities provide services on our behalf (e.g. administrative, management, operational, processing, support, or other services). For instance, we may use such third parties to host message boards, user forums or webpages, to develop software applications, create and maintain databases, send and receive communications on our behalf, or we may retain vendors’ fulfilment houses, or survey, market research and contest services providers. We provide them with a limited amount of information which is necessary in order for them to provide the services required. They are prohibited from using the information for purposes other than to facilitate and carry out the services they have been engaged to provide. These service providers are not permitted to disclose this information to others. Cineplex will strive to protect Personal Information shared with third parties by contractual agreements.
Your Personal Information may be used by Cineplex and shared with parties connected with the contemplated or actual financing, insuring, sale, assignment or other disposal of all or part of Cineplex's business or assets, including for the purposes of permitting such parties to determine whether to proceed or continue with such transaction or business relationship, to fulfill reporting, audit, legal and/or other requirements or, in the case of sale or assignment, the use and sharing by those parties for substantially the same purposes as described in this Privacy Policy.
Cineplex may also share Personal Information as necessary to meet legal, audit, regulatory, insurance, security or other similar requirements. For instance, Cineplex may be compelled to disclose Personal Information in response to a law, regulation, court order, subpoena, valid demand, search warrant, government investigation or other legally valid request or enquiry. We may also share information to our accountants, auditors, agents and lawyers in connection with the enforcement or protection of our legal rights. We also reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities that we, in good faith, believe to be unlawful or to law enforcement, in an emergency or where required or permitted by law.
All Cineplex employees, agents, contractors, service providers, partners and representatives who have access to your Personal Information are required to protect the information in a manner that is consistent with this and any other policy and/or procedure, in effect from time to time.
Your Consent
Consent to the collection, use and sharing of Personal Information may be given in various ways. Consent may be express (e.g. orally, electronically or on a form you may sign describing the intended uses and sharing of Personal Information) or implied (e.g. when you provide information necessary for a service you have requested (such as providing us with your name, phone number and/or email for use by our lost and found services), or in some circumstances where notice has been provided to you about our intentions with respect to your Personal Information and you have not withdrawn your consent for an identified purpose, such as by using an "opt-out" option, subject to applicable laws. Consent may be given by your authorized representative (such as a legal guardian, person having a power of attorney or a mandatary). By providing us with Personal Information, we will deem you to understand this Privacy Policy, and we will deem you to consent to our collection, use and sharing of such Personal Information for the purposes identified or described in this Privacy Policy, if applicable, or otherwise at the time of collection.
Right to Withdraw Consent and Unsubscribe
You may withdraw your consent to our collection, use and sharing of Personal Information at any time, subject to contractual and legal restrictions and reasonable notice. Note that if you withdraw your consent to certain uses of your Personal Information, we may no longer be able to provide you with certain products or services.
Receiving commercial emails and SMS messages from us is optional and you may unsubscribe at any time by (a) following the unsubscribe link in any email or SMS message; (b) changing your communication preferences through your Cineplex Account (if applicable); or (c) contacting us as indicated in the How to Contact Us section of this Privacy Policy.
If you provide us with your mailing address, you may receive periodic mailings from us, or our business partners, with information on new products and services or upcoming events. If you do not wish to receive such mail from us, please change your preferences on the Applications or Websites, or contact us as indicated in the How to Contact Us section of this Privacy Policy.
Security
We protect your Personal Information using physical, electronic or procedural security measures as are appropriate and proportional to the sensitivity of the information in our custody or control, including safeguards to protect Personal Information against loss or theft, as well as unauthorized access, sharing, copying, use, or modification. Cineplex and its employees, agents, contractors, legal, accounting or other service providers, partners, representatives and mandataries who require access to your Personal Information in order to fulfill their job requirements will have access to your Personal Information. You transmit or provide all Personal Information entirely at your own risk.
On our Applications and Websites we store subscriber and password information in a secure manner not accessible to browsers, behind password protection, or off-line. We endeavor to use industry-standard encryption technologies when transferring and receiving consumer data exchanged with our Applications and Websites.
Transfer of Personal Information outside your Country of Residence
Your Personal Information may in some cases be transferred to jurisdictions outside your country of residence. As a result, you understand that your Personal Information will be subject to the laws of other jurisdictions than your country of residence and may be available without notice to you to foreign government authorities under lawful orders and laws applicable in such jurisdictions. Regardless of the company or person who processes your information and where it is processed, we will take steps to protect your Personal Information in accordance with applicable data protection laws and this Privacy Policy.
Note to Parents - Children's Privacy
Protecting children's privacy is important to us. For that reason, we do not collect Personal Information on our Applications or Websites from those children we actually know are under 13 years of age. In addition, no part of our Applications or Websites are targeted to attract anyone under 13 years of age. We request that children under 13 years of age do not disclose or provide any Personal Information. If we discover such information, we will delete the child's Personal Information from our records. If for any reason we believe a user may be under the age of 13 we reserve the right to request proof of age of such user. If such proof is not provided, or if it is discovered a user is under the age of 13 all Personal Information of that user shall be deleted from our servers and associated systems and we reserve the right to limit and/or ban such user from our Applications or Websites. Notwithstanding the foregoing, Cineplex may from time to time conduct, sponsor, co-sponsor or participate in contests and/or promotions which may be open to entrants of all ages, including children under the age of 13. During such contests and/or promotions, Cineplex makes special efforts to encourage children to consult with their parents before providing Personal Information and in each case parental consent must be obtained in order for any such entry or participation to be valid. Cineplex also believes that parents should supervise their children's online activities and consider using parental control tools, available from online services and software manufacturers, to help provide a child-friendly online environment. These tools may also prevent children from disclosing online their name, address, and other Personal Information without parental permission. For additional information about parental control tools, please visit https://www.fosi.org.
Privacy Policies of Third Parties and External Links
The Applications and Websites contain links to a number of third party websites that are not owned or controlled by Cineplex and this Privacy Policy does not apply to such websites or the use of any data by such websites. Should you decide to navigate to any websites or webpage external to the Applications or Websites, you do so entirely at your own risk. External links to third party websites or webpages accessed through our Applications or Websites, as well as the content on such third party websites or webpages, are not investigated, assured, guaranteed, verified, monitored, recommended or endorsed by Cineplex. Cineplex provides these links merely as a convenience to you and to other visitors to our Websites, and the inclusion of such links does not imply that we endorse or recommend such websites or webpages. We specifically disclaim any liability, obligation or responsibility whatsoever for the content or use of such third-party websites or webpages. We encourage you to familiarize yourself with the privacy statements provided by all third parties prior to providing them with information or taking advantage of an offer or promotion.
Please note that the online purchase of theatre tickets through third-party websites, applications, or services may be governed by terms and conditions and privacy practices as set by such third-party website, application, or service. Third party websites and services are not within the scope of this Privacy Policy and Cineplex expressly disclaims any liability, obligation or responsibility whatsoever for the content or use of such third-party websites or services.
Policy Changes
This Privacy Policy may be revised from time to time as Cineplex deems necessary or advisable in its sole discretion. We will post any privacy policy changes on our Applications and Websites and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice. You will continue to have the ability to opt out of new non-essential uses or disclosures. If you are concerned with how your Personal Information is used, we encourage you to bookmark this site and to periodically review our Privacy Policy, or contact us as described below to obtain a current copy of our Privacy Policy.
Access and Correction
Cineplex respects your right to access and correct your Personal Information. If you have an account with us, you can log into your Cineplex Account at any time to access and update the information you have provided to us. Additionally, Cineplex complies with all laws regarding access and correction. If you need assistance updating your Personal Information, please contact us using the contact information detailed in the How to Contact Us section below. Please clearly indicate the Personal Information that you wish to review or have changed. We will to reply to your request as soon as reasonably possible.
How to Contact Us
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, or about our practices with respect to Personal Information, if you wish us to stop communicating with you, or if you wish to access or correct your Personal Information, please notify us.
by email at privacy@cineplex.com
telephone us at 1-877-323-6645
or by mail at:
1303 Yonge Street  Toronto, ON M4T 2Y9 Attn: Chief Privacy Officer
© 2018 Cineplex Entertainment LP
Staying home tonight?
Tickets are available at box office based on availability.
